The first thing that makes the Ethical Cam Community different from other
webcam agencies
is that it was founded by Georgia and I, so as webcam models are self, our
experience
informs everything that we do.
We offer photo shoots, events and well-being weekends, this is a really amazing
place to
meet the other members and mentors and yeah it's not just about Cameron, it's
about everything
else as well and the social side of things too.
Every month we have a variety of Zoom training calls and socials either hosted
by Georgia
or myself or experts in the webcam, sex work or different well-being fields
such as the
less cause, nutrition, mental health, goal setting, manifestation and anything
else you
need to do with webcam work.
All of our Zoom training sessions are recorded and we upload all of these to
our exclusive
members area which you will have access to.
In our members area we have articles, we have blogs, we have a welcome course
and other courses
that is really beneficial to a new webcam girl and we have so much content in
there that
will really help you and give you so much knowledge when starting on your new
journey.
When you start your journey with the Ethical Cam Community you'll be assigned
one of our
experienced mentors.
So one of these mentors is somebody from within our community that will guide
you along on
your journey.
We have various WhatsApp groups where you can keep up to date with everything
that's going
on with the Ethical Cam Community either socially or work-wise with training,
regular competitions
that we put on or any events or anything else that we have running.
We are incredibly proud of all our members and the support and the sisterhood
that they
show within our WhatsApp groups at all our social events and we really think
that this
sets us aside from other agencies.
The energy in the group is just amazing and you'll really find a great group of
friends.
Another amazing thing that sets us aside from other agencies is that we do
everything
with love and we really celebrate and respect the individuality and the
diversity of our
members and we will never ever want anyone to do anything they feel
uncomfortable with.
We always teach our members to stand in your power and only ever do what you're
happy to
do.
Right here at the UCC we're really passionate about bringing our whole selves
so that you
can bring your whole selves to this community.
As a licensed psychotherapist I bring all things mental health and well-being
to try
and offer the most holistic support to all our members.
And what I feel like I offer to our members is my experience.
I've been in this industry for the best part of 10 years and when I started I
was completely
on my own with no support so I've been through all of the ups and downs and the
mistakes
and the lessons and I feel like I can really bring the lessons that I've learnt
to you
ladies.
And finally what sets us apart from other groups or being an independent webcam
model
is that we offer daily pay.
So what you make on one day you get paid straight into your bank account the
next.